{"data":[{"question":"I have often been there.' '________'","a":"So did she","b":"Neither does she","c":"So has she","d":"Nor has she","answer":"3","explain":"\n- To agree with a positive statement: so + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I can't remember anything.' '_________'","a":"Neither can I","b":"So can I","c":"Neither do I","d":"Neither am I","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun\n\n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I could do with another drink.' '_________'","a":"Neither did I","b":"Nor could I","c":"So could I","d":"Do do I","answer":"3","explain":"\n- To agree with a positive statement: so + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"She is not ready yet.' '_________'","a":"Neither have","b":"Nor I am","c":"Neither am I","d":"So am I","answer":"3","explain":"\n- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I don't like living in this place.' '_________'","a":"Neither do I","b":"So do I","c":"Nor am I","d":"Nor I am","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun\n\n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I like swimming in the mornings.' _________","a":"So do I","b":"Neither I","c":"Nor do I","d":"So would I","answer":"1","explain":"\n- To agree with a positive statement: so + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I'd like to go to the cinema.' '_________'","a":"So do I","b":"So would I","c":"So will I","d":"So did I","answer":"2","explain":"\n- To agree with a positive statement: so + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement \n- I'd like= I would like= auxiliary verb is \"would\" ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I'd like to go.' '_________'","a":"So did I","b":"So would I","c":"Neither would I","d":"So will I","answer":"2","explain":"\n- To agree with a positive statement: so + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement \n- I'd like= I would like= auxiliary verb is \"would\"","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I can't go with her.' '________'","a":"Neither can I","b":"Neither do I","c":"So can I","d":"So do I","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun\n\n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"They couldn't do it'. '________'","a":"So could I","b":"Neither could I","c":"Neither am I","d":"Neither did I","answer":"2","explain":"\n- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}